SHELDON:
Please, Penny, enough. I have to sleep.
PENNY:
Okay, well, you were great. Thanks.
Oh. Listen, don't go in Sheldon's room.
He's not wearing bottoms.
[KNOCKING]
Sheldon, you wanna catch me up again?
(Gablehauser:)People, I am very busy today.
I realize that, but it is your job
as head of the department...
...to mediate all intra-departmental
disputes.
University Policy Manual, Chapter 4,
subsection 2:
"Mediation
of Intra-departmental Disputes."
[SCOFFS]
(Gablehauser:)Fine.
Dr. Winkle, what colorful name
did you call Dr. Cooper this time?
(Leslie:)Dr. Dumb-ass.
Dr. Cooper, Dr. Winkle apologizes.
- No, she doesn't.
- No, I don't.
(Sheldon:)Here's the problem. I was clearly signed up
to use the mainframe in Buckman 204...